aisquared.com 2014-12-01

# Ai Squared - We've got accessibility covered

Thank you for visiting aisquared.com. We are committed to respecting the privacy of our users and we strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement outlines the online data collection and usage policies that apply to aisquared.com, and applies solely to the information we collect there. By using our website, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement. 

## What personal information is collected from you through our Website

Unless you provide it to us, we do not collect any personal information about you when you visit our website. If you place an online order or request a free trial of our software, we do ask for information such as your name, postal address, telephone number and e-mail address. If you do give us your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from Ai Squared or other vendors with information on upgrades and new or related products. 

## Links to other sites

Our sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. Ai Squared is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from aisquared.com. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

## About cookies

A cookie is a small file that a Website puts on your computer’s hard drive so that it can remember you at a later time. This file contains nothing more than a 32-digit code. It does not contain your name, address, or any other personal information. Cookies are a standard part of Internet use and allow server computers to recognize your computer’s browser when you return to our site. For example, cookies allow us to retain items you’ve placed in your shopping cart, so if you leave to view other areas on our site, or other websites, you won’t have to start shopping from scratch when you return. 

## Security

We use industry-standard methods to protect your personal financial information from unauthorized access. When you enter sensitive information on an order form (such as a credit card number), that information is encrypted, and is protected with 128-bit encryption SSL technology. Information is then stored on a computer behind our “firewall” in a secure location. 

## Internet Logging

ZoomText 9.1 features an internet logging capability that anonymously sends Ai Squared information to help improve ZoomText and track down issues in the field. This logging captures any ZoomText errors, your version of ZoomText, and the operating system you are running.  The information is sent to us encrypted with industry standard MD-5 encryption technology. None of your information is plain text. If you would like to opt out, simply uncheck the option to “Enable ZoomText Error Reporting” on your first launch of ZoomText. 

## How to update your personal information

You can help Ai Squared maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us when you change your name, address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information, or you prefer to stop receiving communication from Ai Squared, feel free to contact us: 

## Mail:

Ai Squared   
P.O. Box 669   
Manchester Center, VT 05255 

## Phone:

802-362-3612 

## Fax:

802-362-1670 

## Email:

## Website:
